yourbillbuddy.com 2014-11-27

# Privacy Policy - Compare Mobile Tariff Plans - Reduce Mobile Phone Bills |YourBillBuddy

## Know your Best Plan & Save Money!

Watch our patented recommendation engine show the best mobile plans in a few seconds. Now. FREE!

## Upload Mobile Bill

Upload your e-bill now:

Or

## Enter Call Details

Don't have an e-bill? Enter your outgoing call/SMS details:

## Enter Call Details

Enter your outgoing call/SMS/3G details:

**Introduction**

Girnar NewTel solutions Pvt. Ltd has created this Privacy Policy in order to disclose its use of consumer data collected about you. This Privacy Policy is effective as of September 15, 2005. Any questions regarding this policy should be directed by email to feedback@newtel.in. You may also contact Newtel at 143, Sobha Lavender, Bellandur,Bangalore - 560 103,INDIA,Phone: +91 98864 72714. The following discloses Newtel's information gathering and dissemination practices for its marketing website. 

**Information Collected and Received**

Newtel may collect or receive information about each person who registers with the Newtel website including, but not limited to, user name, password, first and last name, email address, phone number, street address, gender, occupation, and interests. Newtel also collects information on the pages you access and other information you may volunteer, such as survey information. 

**Uses of Information**

We at Newtel are proud of our concern for your privacy and our commitment to protect it. Under no circumstances will we hand over the e-bill to a third party. Newtel will not disclose details of your bills, or calling pattern to any other external third party. 

Newtel may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with Newtel's server and to administer Newtel's web site. Your IP address may also be used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information. Newtel's site's registration form requires users to give Newtel contact information (such as your name and email address) and demographic information (such as your zip code, age, or income level). Newtel uses customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about Newtel's company and promotional material from some of Newtel's partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the user when necessary. Users may choose to opt-out of receiving future mailings. Demographic and profile data may also be collected at Newtel's site. Newtel may use this data to tailor the visitor's experience on Newtel's site, show the visitor content that Newtel thinks you may be interested in, and display content according to your preferences. The demographic and profile data may be shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

The Newtel website may provide certain features ("Features") that enable sending/receiving invites/solicitation messages/reminders to your contacts whose details, as required under the specific Features, are submitted and specifically permitted by you to be so used. Newtel shall use the contact details only for the Feature specifically approved by you. 

**Security**

Newtel uses industry-standard technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged between Newtel and other companies to help ensure its security. This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under Newtel's control. Newtel's servers are backed up regularly and protected by security systems. 

**Cookies**

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Newtel's site uses cookies to keep track of your session, shopping cart, and advertising delivery. Newtel may also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password. Newtel may use an outside ad company to display ads on Newtel's site. These ads may also contain cookies. While Newtel uses cookies in other parts of Newtel's web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by Newtel's ad company and Newtel do not have access to this information. 

**Links**

Newtel may create links to other web sites. Newtel will make a reasonable effort to link only to sites that meet similar standards for maintaining each individual's right to privacy. However, many other sites that are not associated or authorized by Newtel may have links leading to Newtel's site. Newtel cannot control these links and Newtel is not responsible for any content appearing on these sites. 

**Amendments**

Newtel may amend this policy at any time. If Newtel is going to use personally identifiable information collected through Newtel's corporate site in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection Newtel will notify users via email and/or by posting a notice on Newtel's Web site for 30 days. This Agreement may not be otherwise amended except in a writing that specifically refers to this policy and is physically signed by both parties. 

**Contacts**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact feedback@newtel.in. Upon request, Newtel will provide you with access to information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that Newtel collects and maintains about you. This site gives you the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: (i) email: feedback@newtel.in; or (ii) visit www.yourbillbuddy.com. There you can also log into your account to update your contact information. 

**Opt-Out**

Newtel's site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from Newtel. To opt-out of receiving our communications, you can (i) send email to feedback@newtel.in; or (ii) send postal mail to: 143, Sobha Lavender, Bellandur,Bangalore - 560 103,INDIA,Phone: +91 98864 72714.
